let me get the mic on oh I got the mic
on what I let start
over if you're working to take your
Warehouse from good to great you're
going to want to watch this series hi my
name is Aaron ruin I'm the founder and
CEO of ship hero you might know us for
our warehouse management software and we
do have the warehouse management
software that is the most popular and
highest rated for e-commerce Brands
between $5 and $100 million a year in
revenue and the 3pls that serve them
what you might not know is we operate
over a million square ft of warehouses
in North America serving mid and large
siiz e-commerce Brands I'm in one of
those facilities today in Jacksonville
Florida you'll hear from the general
managers in our buildings across the
United States as well as people on the
floor and our remote Ops team as we show
you what they do to satisfy our
customers needs and run a profitable as
scale 3pl doing what we do is nothing
magical right anybody can take a product
put put it in a box and give it to a
carrier it's really about the
relationship that you build with those
customers and being able to follow
through with what you say you're going
to do if you have stragglers or quars
that are still sitting and waiting
coming in the following morning that's
kind of when you want to start looking
into that second shift or replay you
know you don't want slow starts in the
morning you want to come in you want to
rock and roll cuz that first hour or two
of your shift is what's going to make
that shipping day finding those issues
before it stops production on the floor
um through the Q management side of it
it's ensuring that each facility has
work consistently throughout the day so
there's no down time you don't want to
overbill your clients either they don't
like that very much so because this is
your source of Truth meaning this this
tracking system if it's incorrectly
tracked because of the human element you
need to make sure that you're checking
both ends of those transactions so that
when someone's out of the building but
still quote billing hours you don't want
that to happen everything in a warehouse
should have a flow it comes into the
building it comes out of the building
right now our Pickers start at that end
of the building and they finish all the
way at the far end and they put their
tote their carts completed over in this
area however speed is a is a key factor
here as well if I want to get the
numbers out the door I need some people
who are efficient and know how to work
with some speed it's a trial and error
basis we see who's out there we see who
looks good we see who uh Works
efficiently and things like that um and
um we'll bring them back here to B
as soon as they hit our docks we open
these purchase plans and then we
basically go from looking and seeing
what product we have how many we have
back ordered whatever the case may be
for that specific shipping plan we
basically receive the stock in make sure
whether it's allocated to RSP RSC
whatever receiving storing location that
we have and then from there we put into
Overstock we're excited to take you on
this journey we're going to go through
several of our buildings and show you
the best practices we use that will
hopefully help you take your existing
Warehouse that's running well and make
it run even better
[Music]